<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>
		.important {
			color: mediumblue;
			margin-left: 50px;
			background-color: slateblue;
		}
		.ageement {
			background-color: saddlebrown;
		}
	</ui:style>
	<g:VerticalPanel width="100%" height="100%"
		horizontalAlignment="ALIGN_CENTER" verticalAlignment="ALIGN_MIDDLE">
		<g:VerticalPanel>
			<g:VerticalPanel spacing="5" width="500px">
				<g:Label text="Please read terms and conditions of the order you are about to make:" horizontalAlignment="ALIGN_LEFT" />
				<g:ScrollPanel height="400px">
					<g:HTML wordWrap="true" height="100px">TERMS &amp; CONDITIONS
EFFECTIVE:  MAY , 2013
USE OF THE INTERACTIVE 3D PRODUCTS (THE “PRODUCTS”) IS OFFERED TO YOU, THE CUSTOMER, CONDITIONAL ON YOUR ACCEPTANCE WITHOUT MODIFICATION OF THE TERMS, CONDITIONS, AND NOTICES CONTAINED BELOW. YOUR USE OF THIS PRODUCT CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO ALL SUCH TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND THE OFFER OF SERVICES TO YOU IS CONDITIONED UPON YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH TERMS AND CONDITIONS.
DEFINITIONS
When used in these Terms with the initial letters capitalized, the following terms have the following meanings:
3D Condo Explorer:  means 3D Condo Explorer, Inc.  In these Terms, 3D Condo Explorer may also be referred to through the use of “We” or “Our.”
Confidential Information:  means all information disclosed by You to 3D Condo Explorer or by 3D Condo Explorer to You which is in tangible form and labeled “confidential” (or with a similar legend) or which a reasonable person would understand to be confidential given the nature of the information and circumstances of disclosure.  
Documentation:  means any written or electronic documentation, images, video, text or sounds specifying the functionalities of the Service provided or made available by 3D Condo Explorer to End-Users through the Site or otherwise.
End-User: means any person or entity using the Service who may also be referred to through the use of “You” and “Your”.
Other Services:  means products, services and data provided by third party which the Service links to, or which You may connect to or enable in conjunction with the Service.
Service:  means 3D Condo Explorer customer service solution and tools provided by 3D Condo Explorer, including Software and Documentation.  Any new or modified features added to the Service or updates and enhancements to the Service (“Updates”) are also subject to these Terms and We reserve the right to deploy Updates at any time.
Product:  means any of the Interactive 3D Products offered by 3D Condo Explorer Inc.
Software:  means software provided by 3D Condo Explorer that allows an End User to use any functionality in connection with the Service.
Your Data:  means all electronic data, text, or other materials submitted to the Service by You in connection with Your use of 3D Condo Explorer Service. 
GENERAL CONDITIONS; ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE SERVICE
You agree not to (a) modify or decompile the Product or otherwise attempt to gain unauthorized access to the Service; (b) use the Service in any unlawful manner which includes sending spam or junk mail, transmitting, linking to, storing any content that is abusive, unlawful, or which infringes any person’s intellectual property rights; (e) attempt to hack, reverse engineer or otherwise discover the source code of any software making up the Service; or (g) try to use, or use the Service in violation of these Terms. A high speed Internet connection is required for proper transmission of the Service. You are responsible for procuring and maintaining the network connections that connect Your network to the Service, including, but not limited to, “browser” software that supports protocols used by 3D Condo Explorer. We are not responsible for notifying You, End Users, of any upgrades, fixes or enhancements to any such software. We assume no responsibility for the reliability or performance of any connections as described in this section.
DATA PRIVACY AND SECURITY; CONFIDENTIALITY
You and 3D Condo Explorer will protect each other’s Confidential Information from unauthorized use, access or disclosure in the same manner as each protects its own Confidential Information, but with no less than reasonable care.
You are aware and agree that We collect certain information about You as well as Your devices, computers and use of the Service and the service providers. Any third party service providers 3D Condo Explorer utilizes will only be given access to Your Data as is reasonably necessary to provide the Service and will be subject to confidentiality obligations.
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS
The Site, including all information and content thereon such as text, data, wallpaper, icons, characters, artwork, images, photographs, graphics, messages, software and the HTML used to generate the pages (collectively, “Materials”), are the property of 3D Condo Explorer or our suppliers or licensors and is protected by patent, trademark and/or copyright under Canadian and/or foreign laws. 
THIRD PARTY SERVICES
This Product may contain hyper-links to web sites operated by parties other than 3D Condo Explorer. Such hyperlinks are provided for your reference only. Moreover, the Product may contain third party products, applications, software, products, networks, systems, directories, websites, and databases such as Google Earth platform which is integrated directly into Your 3D Condo Explorer Service. 3D Condo Explorer does not control such web sites and is not responsible for their contents or your use of them. 3D Condo Explorer’s inclusion of hyper-links and use of such web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such web sites or any association with their operators.
PAYMENTS
3D Condo Explorer uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing and this intermediary is not permitted to store, retain or use Your billing information except to process Your credit card information for 3D Condo Explorer.
REFUND/RETURN POLICY
Considering the character of the Services provided, no refunds will be provided to You if You elect to terminate the use of the Services purchased. Only if the refusal to use the Services is reasonable We will consider a refund in form of credits that can be spent as payments for the Services purchased from 3D Condo Explorer.
 OUR RIGHT TO MODIFY THESE TERMS 
3D Condo Explorer reserves the right to change the Terms and Conditions under which this Product is offered without notice and you agree to accept and be bound by those Terms and Conditions that are in effect at the time of your use of 3D Condo Explorer’s Product and services.
LAW AND JURISDICTION
Any disputes arising out of or relating to these Terms, use of the Site, and the services offered via the Site shall be resolved in accordance with the laws of the Province of Ontario without regard to its conflict of law rules. Any disputes, actions or proceedings relating to these Terms or your access to or use of the Site must be brought before the courts of the Province of Ontario in the City of Toronto, Ontario and you irrevocably consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of such courts. 3D Condo Explorer makes no claim that the Site may be lawfully viewed or that content may be lawfully downloaded. 
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES
YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK WITH RESPECT TO YOUR USE OF THE SITE, WHICH IS PROVIDED “AS IS.” WE DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS AND ENDORSEMENTS OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH REGARD TO INFORMATION ACCESSED FROM OR VIA THE SITE INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ALL CONTENT AND MATERIALS, AND FUNCTIONS AND SERVICES PROVIDED ON THE SITE, ALL OF WHICH ARE PROVIDED WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES CONCERNING THE AVAILABILITY, ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS OR USEFULNESS OF CONTENT OR INFORMATION, UNINTERRUPTED ACCESS, AND ANY WARRANTIES OF TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. WE DO NOT WARRANT THAT THE SITE OR ITS FUNCTIONING OR THE CONTENT AND MATERIALS OR THE SERVICES MADE AVAILABLE THEREBY WILL BE TIMELY, SECURE, UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE, OR THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED. WE MAKE NO WARRANTY THAT THE SITE WILL MEET USERS' EXPECTATIONS OR REQUIREMENTS. NO ADVICE, RESULTS, INFORMATION OR MATERIALS, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY MADE HEREIN. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH THE SITE, YOUR SOLE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE SITE. ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SITE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
NEITHER 3D CONDO EXPLORER NOR ANY OF ITS THEIR OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, REPRESENTATIVES OR SUBCONTRACTORS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR LIABILITY RESULTING, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, FROM DELAYS OR INTERRUPTIONS DUE TO ELECTRONIC OR MECHANICAL EQUIPMENT FAILURES, DENIAL OF SERVICE ATTACKS, DATE DATA PROCESSING FAILURES, TELECOMMUNICATIONS OR INTERNET PROBLEMS, UTILITY FAILURES OR PROBLEMS, DEFECTS, WEATHER, STRIKES, WALKOUTS, FIRE, ACTS OF GOD, RIOTS, ARMED CONFLICTS, ACTS OF WAR OR OTHER LIKE CAUSES BEYOND THE REASONABLE CONTROL OF 3D CONDO EXPLORER. 3D CONDO EXPLORER IS NOT LIABLE OF ANY INTERRUPTION IN THE THIRD PARTY SERVICES IT DEPENDS ON. 3D CONDO EXPLORER SHALL HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY TO PROVIDE ACCESS TO THIS PRODUCT WHILE THE INTERRUPTION OF THIS PRODUCT DUE TO ANY SUCH CAUSE SHALL CONTINUE. 3D CONDO EXPLORER MAY DISCONTINUE PROVIDING ACCESS TO THIS PRODUCT AT ANY TIME. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES AND UNDER NO LEGAL THEORY (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) WILL EITHER PARTY TO THESE TERMS, OR THEIR AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS OR LICENSORS BE LIABLE TO THE OTHER PARTY OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHER SIMILAR DAMAGES, INCLUDING LOST PROFITS, LOST SALES OR BUSINESS, LOST DATA, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION OR ANY OTHER LOSS INCURRED BY SUCH PARTY OR THIRD PARTY IN CONNECTION WITH THESE TERMS OR THE SERVICE, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER SUCH PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF OR COULD HAVE FORESEEN SUCH DAMAGES.
You agree to release, defend, indemnify and hold 3D Condo Explorer harmless from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses or expenses, including reasonable attorneys' fees and costs, arising out of or in any way connected with your access to or use of this Product or any Product Information.

These Terms and Conditions, together with those incorporated herein or referred to herein, constitute the entire agreement between you and 3D Condo Explorer with respect to this Product and supersede all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral, or written, between you and 3D Condo Explorer with respect to this Product.

</g:HTML>
				</g:ScrollPanel>
				<g:HorizontalPanel width="100%"
					horizontalAlignment="ALIGN_LEFT" spacing="5">
					<g:Cell verticalAlignment="ALIGN_MIDDLE">
						<g:Button width="75px" ui:field="buttonCancel">Cancel</g:Button>
					</g:Cell>
					<g:Cell horizontalAlignment="ALIGN_RIGHT" width="100%">
						<g:HorizontalPanel spacing="15">
						<g:Button width="75px" ui:field="buttonAgree" text="I Agree"/>
					</g:HorizontalPanel>
					</g:Cell>
					<g:Cell horizontalAlignment="ALIGN_RIGHT" verticalAlignment="ALIGN_MIDDLE">
						<g:HorizontalPanel spacing="5">
							<g:Button text="&lt;&lt; Prev" width="75px" ui:field="buttonPrev">Prev</g:Button>
							<g:Button width="75px" ui:field="buttonProceed" enabled="false">Proceed</g:Button>
						</g:HorizontalPanel>
					</g:Cell>
				</g:HorizontalPanel>
			</g:VerticalPanel>
		</g:VerticalPanel>
	</g:VerticalPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 